Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) PE.021
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO)
1949-2007
1955-2000
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library
PE.021
13.25 Linear Feet in 12 record cartons and 3 shared boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) (1947-2007, bulk 1955-2000) is an artificial collection, collected and assembled by the Tamiment Library over the course of several decades. The collection consists of constitutions, by-laws, convention proceedings, press releases, reports, and rosters as well as printed ephemera such as fliers, brochures, circular letters, newspapers clippings, pamphlets, and other publications. The material generally comes from the AFL-CIO's national body as well as its various departments and committees. There is also material from the governing city, state and central federations of the AFL-CIO from around the country, notably from the New York State AFL-CIO. The collection also contains material from the New York City Central Labor Council, a labor membership organization for New York City unions.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Custodial History
The provenance of the materials is varied. Items were obtained through purchases, donations, standing orders with publishers, arrangements with labor unions and other organizations, exchanges with other libraries, and through ongoing collecting by Tamiment staff.
Historical Note
The AFL-CIO was formed when the American Federation of Labor (AFL) and the Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) merged in 1955. The AFL was formed in 1886 and was led by Samuel Gompers as a more traditional union that organized workers along craft lines. The CIO, initially a committee within the AFL called the Committee for Industrial Organization, broke away from the AFL in the late 1930s after disputes in how to organize all the workers of one industry into the same union. George Meany, the president of the AFL, was elected to serve as the first president of the newly merged AFL-CIO. He was succeeded by Lane Kirkland in 1979. As a voluntary federation of international labor unions, the AFL-CIO represents nearly all unionized employees in the United States and Canada. The AFL-CIO lobbies on behalf of organized labor and mediates disputes between member unions. It holds quadrennial conventions and member unions are proportionately represented with delegates who attend and vote. John Sweeney was elected as president in 1995, this was the AFL-CIO's first contested election. When Sweeney retired in 2009, Richard Trumka, of the United Mine Workers of America was elected president.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into three series. All series are arranged alphabetically. The series arrangement of the records is as follows:
Series I: National Files, 1950-2005
Series II: State, Regional, and Central Council Files, 1956-2007
Series III: New York City Central Labor Council Files, 1959-2005
Scope and Content Note
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) (1947-2007, bulk 1955-2000) consists of material that was generated by the AFL-CIO at the national, state, and municipal levels. The collection contains material from various departments and committees, and includes constitutions, by-laws, convention proceedings, reports, rosters, and press releases as well as printed ephemera such as fliers, circular letters, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, and publications.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials in this collection have been compiled by the Tamiment Library. The accession numbers associated with this collection are NPA.2000.334, NPA.2001.040, and NPA.2003.085.
In 2025, materials from accession 2019.056, which is associated with Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Subjects (PE 029), were transferred to this collection
Labor unions; Labor unions -- United States.; Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Press releases.; Rosters.; Public employees.; Constitutions.; Circular letters.; Printed ephemera.; Fliers (printed matter); Pamphlets.; Publications (documents); Civil rights.; Labor unions -- New York (State); Labor movement.; AFL-CIO; AFL-CIO. Committee on Political Education; AFL-CIO. New York City Central Labor Council
- Series I: National Files, 1949-2005; 10.5 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes and 1 shared manuscript box
  - African-American Labor Center, 1970-1995, undated (Box 1)
  - The American Federationist: Reprints, 1957-1969, undated (Box 1)
  - The American Federationist: Reprints, 1970-1989 (Box 1)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1965-1975 (Box 1)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1976-1979 (Box 1)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1980-1985 (Box 1)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1986-1990 (Box 1)
  - American Labor Health Association, undated (Box 1)
  - Asian-American Free Labor Institute, 1980, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance, 1992-1994 (Box 1)
  - Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance, 1996-2005 (Box 1)
  - Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance: Almeda County Chapter, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance: Los Angeles Chapter, 1994-1995 (Box 1)
  - Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance: New York Chapter, 1996-2002 (Box 1)
  - Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance: San Francisco Chapter, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance: Seattle Chapter, undated (Box 1)
  - Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance: Twin Cities Chapter, undated (Box 1)
  - Auxiliary Publications, 1959, undated (Box 1)
  - Brochures, 1950s-1990s, undated (Box 1)
  - Building and Construction Trades Department, 1963-1980 (Box 1)
  - Building and Construction Trades Department: The Builders: Special Reports, circa 1970s-1980s, undated (Box 1)
  - Building and Construction Trades Department: Conventions, 1963-1983 (Box 1)
  - Building and Construction Trades Department: Davis-Bacon Act, 1979, undated (Box 1)
  - Building and Construction Trades Department: Legislature (Publications Relating to), 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Building and Construction Trades Department: Legislature, circa 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - Building and Construction Trades Department: Pamphlets and Publications, 1970-1997, undated (Box 1)
  - Building and Construction Trades Department: Press Releases, 1981-1986, undated (Box 1)
  - Building and Construction Trades Department: Publication Order Forms, 1986-1992 (Box 1)
  - Circular Letters, 1962-1977, undated (Box 1)
  - Civil Rights, 1956-1963 (Box 1)
  - Civil Rights/Department of Civil Rights: Conferences, 1957-1985 (Box 2)
  - Civil Rights/Department of Civil Rights: Executive Council Statements and Reports on, 1956-1989, undated (Box 2)
  - Civil Rights/Department of Civil Rights: Fliers and Reprinted Articles and Brochures, 1958-1965, undated (Box 2)
  - Civil Rights/Department of Civil Rights: Pamphlets and Publications, 1964-1970, undated (Box 2)
  - Civil Rights/Department of Civil Rights: Resolutions Adopted at Conventions, 1957-1981 (Box 2)
  - Committee for Gas Safety, undated (Box 2)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Brochures, 1959-1980, undated (Box 2)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE): By-Laws, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Cartoons, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Financial Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Fliers and Ephemera, circa 1960-1980s, undated (Box 2)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Memos and Bulletins, 1958-1980 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Pamphlets and Publications, undated (Box 2)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Speakers' Handbook, 1958-1966 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Voting Records, 1960-1964 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Safety and Occupational Health, 1971, undated (Box 2)
  - Committee on the Evolution of Work, 1983, 1985, undated (Box 2, Box Shared Tamiment 191, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, 1960-1985 (Box 2)
  - Conferences, 1987-2001 (Box 2)
  - Constitutions, 1955-1959 (Box 2)
  - Constitutions, 1961-1977 (Box 2)
  - Constitutions, 1983-1993 (Box 2)
  - Conventions (Merger Convention), 1955 (Box 2)
  - Conventions (Merger Convention AFL and CIO): Newspaper Clippings and Articles on, 1955-1956, undated (Box 2)
  - Conventions (I), 1955 (Box 2)
  - Conventions (II), 1955 (Box 2)
  - Conventions, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Conventions, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Conventions, 1961-1969 (Box 2)
  - Conventions, 1971-1979 (Box 2)
  - Conventions, 1985-1995 (Box 2)
  - Conventions, 1995-2005 (Box 3, Box Shared Tamiment 191, Folder 7)
  - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Scientific, Professional and Cultural Employees, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Department for Professional Employees, 1979-1997, undated (Box 3)
  - Department for Professional Employees: Bibliographies, 1978, 1983 (Box 3)
  - Department for Professional Employees: Pamphlets and Publications, 1981-1986, undated (Box 3)
  - Department for Professional Employees: Salaried and Professional Women, 1981-1996, undated (Box 3)
  - Department for Professional Employees: Surveys and Statistics (I), 1978 (Box 3)
  - Department for Professional Employees: Surveys and Statistics (II), 1979-1990 (Box 3)
  - Department of Community Services/Community Service Activities (I), undated (Box 3)
  - Department of Community Services/Community Service Activities (II), undated (Box 3)
  - Department of Community Services/Community Service Activities, 1950-1969 (Box 3)
  - Department of Community Services/Community Service Activities, 1970-1994 (Box 3)
  - Department of Economic Research, 1981-1983, undated (Box 3)
  - Department of Economic Research, 1985-1989 (Box 3)
  - Department of Economic Research, 1990-1992 (Box 3)
  - Department of Economic Research, 1993-1996 (Box 3)
  - Department of Economic Research: AFL-CIO Reviews the Issues, 1988-1991 (Box 3)
  - Department of Education: Circular Letters, 1956-1990, undated (Box 3)
  - Department of Education: Conferences and Summer Schools, 1956-1999 (Box 3)
  - Department of Education: Film Division, 1956-1966, undated (Box 3)
  - Department of Education: Film Division, 1971-1992 (Box 3)
  - Department of Education: Fliers, 1958, undated (Box 3)
  - Department of Education: Labor and Worker Education Curriculum, undated (Box 3)
  - Department of Education: Merit Scholarships, 1959-1963, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Department of Education: News and Views Reprints, 1956-1964, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of Education: Pamphlets and Publications, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of Education: Pamphlets and Publications, 1959-1969 (Box 4)
  - Department of Education: Pamphlets and Publications, 1980-1989 (Box 4)
  - Department of Education: Songbooks, 1974-1983, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of Education: Training Programs, 1965, 1989, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of Information, 1985-1995, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of International Affairs, 1960-1962, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of International Affairs, 1967-1991 (Box 4)
  - Department of Legislation, 1960-1991 (Box 4)
  - Department of Legislation: Bulletins ("Issue/Legislative Alert"), 1957-1995 (Box 4)
  - Department of Legislation: Fact Sheets, 1965-1995 (Box 4)
  - Department of Legislation: Labor Looks at Congress, 1956-1969 (Box 4)
  - Department of Legislation: Labor Looks at Congress, 1971-1977 (Box 4)
  - Department of Legislation: Lobbying, 1983-1984, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of Legislation: Statements and Testimonies, 1958-1985 (Box 4)
  - Department of Occupational Safety, Health and Social Security, 1985-1989, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of Organization and Field Services, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of Organization and Field Services, 1987-1994 (Box 4)
  - Department of Publications/Publications and Materials Office, 1960-1978, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of Research, 1958-1967 (Box 4)
  - Department of Research: Pamphlets and Publications, 1960-1969 (Box 4)
  - Department of Research: Pamphlets and Publications, 1956-1959, undated (Box 4)
  - Department of Social Security, 1957-1969 (Box 5)
  - Department of Urban Affairs, 1975-1978 (Box 5)
  - Donahue, Thomas R. (Secretary-Treasurer), 1979-1982 (Box 5)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Fund Committee, undated (Box 5)
  - Elections (US): Platform Proposals of the AFL-CIO to the Democratic and Republican National Elections, 1964-1972 (Box 5)
  - Elections (US): Platform Proposals to the Democratic and Republican National Conventions, 1976-1980 (Box 5)
  - Elections (US): Review of the Issues and Candidates, 1984, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Ethical Practices Committee, 1957-1958, undated (Box 5)
  - Executive Council: Publications and Reports, 1959-1990, undated (Box 5)
  - Executive Council: Speeches, 1979-1990 (Box 5)
  - Executive Council: Statements Adopted and Resolutions, 1958-1969 (Box 5)
  - Executive Council: Statements Adopted and Resolutions, 1970-1977 (Box 5)
  - Executive Council: Statements Adopted and Resolutions, 1981-1983 (Box 5)
  - Executive Council: Statements Adopted and Resolutions, 1984-1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive Council: Statements Adopted and Resolutions, 1990-1993 (Box 5)
  - "Fairness at Eastern Campaign", 1989 (Box 5)
  - Farm Labor Organizing Committee, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Fliers and Ephemera, 1949-1990s, undated (Box 5)
  - Food and Allied Service Trade Department, undated (Box 5)
  - Food and Allied Service Trades Department, 1985-1989 (Box 5)
  - Food and Allied Service Trades Department: Games, undated (Box 5)
  - Food and Beverage Trade Department (I), circa 1980s-1990s, undated (Box 5)
  - Food and Beverage Trade Department (II), circa 1980s-1990s, undated (Box 5)
  - Free Trade Union Institute, 1986, 1995, undated (Box 5)
  - Frontlash (Student Group of the AFL-CIO), 1989 (Box 5)
  - George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1994-1997 (Box 5)
  - George Meany Memorial Archives, 1995, undated (Box 5)
  - Government Employees Council, undated (Box 5)
  - Housing Committee, 1960, 1969, undated (Box 5)
  - Housing Investment Trust, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Human Resources Development Institute, 1996, undated (Box 5)
  - Industrial Union Department, 1956-1989, undated (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Briefs (on Occupational Safety and Health Act), circa 1970-1972 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Collective Bargaining Agreements, Survey of, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Conferences, 1956-1959 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Conferences, 1961-1969 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Constitutions, 1961-1986, undated (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Conventions, 1955-1961 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Fliers and Brochures, undated (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Legislative Section, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Legislative Section, 1961, circa 1978 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: March on Washington, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Organizational Disputes Agreements, 1955-1956, undated (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Pamphlets and Publications, undated (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Pamphlets and Publications, undated (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Pamphlets and Publications, 1950-1959 (Box 6, Box Shared Tamiment 191, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Pamphlets and Publications, 1960-1969 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Pamphlets and Publications, 1970-1979 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Pamphlets and Publications, 1980-1989 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Reprints from IUD Publications, 1959, 1965-1966, undated (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Research Section (I), 1958 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Research Section (II), 1958 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Union Department: Research Section (III), 1958 (Box 7)
  - Industrial Union Department: Research Section (I), 1959 (Box 7)
  - Industrial Union Department: Research Section (II), 1959 (Box 7)
  - Industrial Union Department: Research Section, 1961-1962 (Box 7)
  - Industrial Union Department: Staff Training Courses, 1957-1959 (Box 7)
  - Industrial Union Department: Staff Training Courses, 1959 (Box 7)
  - International Labor Press Association, 1956-1964 (Box 7)
  - Interviews, 1959, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Joint AFL-CIO Unity Committee, 1955, undated (Box 7)
  - Joint Committee on Library Service to Labor Groups/Libraries, 1960-1989, undated (Box 7)
  - Joint Minimum Wage Committee, 1959, undated (Box 7)
  - Labor's Centennial (I), 1981 (Box 7)
  - Labor's Centennial (II), 1981 (Box 7)
  - Labor/Higher Education Council, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 1991, undated (Box 7)
  - "Labor Solidarity with Chile", undated (Box 7)
  - Labor Studies Center, 1974-1976 (Box 7)
  - Lawyers Coordinating Committee, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Maritime Trades Department, 1961-1969, undated (Box 7)
  - Maritime Trades Department, 1975-1984 (Box 7)
  - Maritime Trades Department: The People's Forum, undated (Box 7)
  - Meany, George (President), 1971-2004, undated (Box 7)
  - Metal Trades Department, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Miller, Hank: 35 Years Outside the AFL-CIO: Lifeline, undated (Box 7)
  - Minutes: General Board Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box 7)
  - Negro Labor Committee, USA, undated (Box 7)
  - New Jersey State Public Employees Committee, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles on, 1955-1969, undated (Box 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles on, 1970-2000 (Box 7, Box Shared Tamiment 191, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles on: Foreign Policy, circa 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Nixon, Richard M. Impeachment, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Office of the General Council, undated (Box 8)
  - Organizing Materials, undated (Box 8)
  - Organizing Institute, 1989-1995, undated (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, undated (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, undated (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1954-1957 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1958-1959 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1960-1965 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1970-1972 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1977-1979 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1980-1984 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1985-1989 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1990-2000 (Box 8, Box Shared Tamiment 191, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases/News Releases, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Press Releases/News Releases, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Box Shared Tamiment 191, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases/News Releases, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Press Releases/News Releases, 1971-1972 (Box 9)
  - Press Releases/News Releases, 1979-1995 (Box 9)
  - Public Employee Department, 1975-1997, undated (Box 9)
  - Public Employee Department: Conventions, 1974-1989 (Box 9)
  - Public Employee Department: Conventions, 1991-1997 (Box 9)
  - Public Employee Department: Facts at a Glance, 1991-1997, undated (Box 9)
  - Public Employee Department: Pamphlets and Publications, 1977-1989, undated (Box 9)
  - Public Employee Department: Pamphlets and Publications, 1990-1992 (Box 9)
  - Public Employee Department: Pamphlets and Publications, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Public Employee Department: Pamphlets and Publications, 1994-1996 (Box 9)
  - Public Employee Department: State Development, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Public Policy Department: Economic Policy Papers, 1997 (Box 9)
  - Public Policy Department: Technical Working Papers (I), 1997 (Box 9)
  - Public Policy Department: Technical Working Papers (II), 1997 (Box 9)
  - Retired Union Employees of America, 1973 (Box 9)
  - "Right to Work" Laws, 1956-1957, undated (Box 9)
  - Rocky Mountain Labor School, 1958, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Rosters: Organizations Affiliated With, 1956-1975 (Box 9)
  - Rosters: Organizations Affiliated with, 1986-1999 (Box 9)
  - School Administrators and Supervisors Organizing Committee, 1973, undated (Box 9)
  - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1959-1977, undated (Box 9)
  - State and Local Central Bodies, 1957-1989, undated (Box 10)
  - State and Local Central Bodies: Rules Governing State Central Bodies, 1955-1973 (Box 10)
  - Statements and Testimonies, 1959-1991 (Box 10)
  - Steward's Manuals, 1958-1978 (Box 10)
  - Steward's Manuals, 1980-1988 (Box 10)
  - Task Force on Labor Law Reform, 1977, undated (Box 10)
  - Task Force on Trade, 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department, 1963-1994, undated (Box 10)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department: Constitutions, 1959-1979 (Box 10)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department: Consumers' Directory, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department: Conventions, 2009 (Box 10)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department: Press Releases, 1962-1990, undated (Box 10)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Council of Greater New York and Long Island, 1961-1968, undated (Box 10)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department of the State of New York, 1955-1988, undated (Box 10)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department of the State of New York: Official Directories Union Made Products and Services, undated (Box 10)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department of the State of New York: Official Directories Union Made Products and Services, 1957-1966 (Box 10)
  - "Union Yes" Campaign, 1991, undated (Box 10)
  - Women's Departments and Auxiliary, 1965-1967, undated (Box 10)
- Series II: State, Regional, and Central Council Files, 1956-2007; 2.25 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 shared oversize box
  - Alabama Labor Council, AFL-CIO, undated (Box 10)
  - Arizona State, AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Baltimore Council of AFL-CIO Unions, undated (Box 10)
  - California Labor Federation, AFL-CIO, 1958-1962 (Box 10)
  - California Labor Federation, AFL-CIO, 1973-1999 (Box 10)
  - Cattaraugus and Allegany Counties Labor Council, undated (Box 10)
  - Central Labor Council of Alameda County (CA), 1959, undated (Box 10)
  - Central Labor Council of Santa Clara County, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Cleveland AFL-CIO Federation of Labor, 1975, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Essex-West Hudson Labor Council, 2000, undated (Box 10)
  - Florida State Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Georgia State AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Greater Louisville Central Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Hawaii State Federation of Labor, AFL-CIO, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Indiana State AFL-CIO, 1958-1960 (Box 10)
  - Kentucky State Federation of Labor, 1958, undated (Box 10)
  - King's County Labor Council, AFL-CIO (Washington State), 1995 (Box Shared Tamiment 184, Folder 32)
  - Long Island Federation of Labor, AFL-CIO, 1963-1967 (Box 10)
  - Los Angeles County Federation of Labor, 1962-1966 (Box 10)
  - Louisiana State Labor Council, 1956 (Box 10)
  - Massachusetts State Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1958-1965 (Box 10)
  - Michigan State AFL-CIO, 1958-1960, undated (Box 11)
  - Minnesota AFL-CIO, 1965-1990 (Box 11)
  - Mississippi AFL-CIO, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
  - Missouri State Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1957-1959 (Box 11)
  - New England Labor Council, 1967 (Box 11)
  - New Jersey State AFL-CIO, circa 1990-2000, undated (Box 11)